Birds chirp and tweet in the background.
Birds sing amidst the lush greenery and thick trees.
Birds chirp softly in the background.
Birds chirp in the background as a person walks through the forest.
Birds sing as a man and woman stand in a grassy field.
Birds are chirping in the background.
A crow caws in the distance as three people stand nearby.
Ambient sounds of nature fill the wooded area.
The man sits quietly, deep in thought among the trees.
Music and tabla play softly in the background.
Tabla music plays softly in the background.
Music plays softly in the background as he holds a bag.
Music and tabla play in the background as he stands in the field.
Music plays softly in the background as three people stand in a field.
Music plays softly in the background.
Music and tabla play softly in the background.
A crow caws in the distance as the man walks.
Laughter fills the air as they embrace on the garden bench.
Wild animals and birds can be heard in the garden.
An owl hoots and a bird chirps in the garden.
Crows caw and birds chirp in the background.
Birds chirp softly in the background of the garden.