Ambient noise fills the background during Episode 16.
Birds chirp softly in the background.
Ambient animal and bird sounds fill the environment.
Birds chirp softly in the background of the forest scene.
Sounds of birds and animals fill the forest.
Birds sing while two women stand in a grassy field.
Birds chirp softly in the background as they hold hands.
A crow caws in the distance.
Ambient animal sounds fill the scene.
Animal sounds are heard in the background.
Tabla music plays softly in the background.
Music plays softly in the background.
The tabla plays softly in the background.
Music and tabla play softly in the background.
Music plays softly in the background.
Sounds of a crow and a goose are heard.
Laughter fills the air.
Sounds of animals are present in the background.
Wild animals and birds create ambient sounds in the background.
Owl and animal sounds are heard in the background.
Crows caw and birds chirp in the background.
Music plays softly in the background.
Music plays softly in the background as three people sit together.
Music plays softly in the background as they sit together.
Sounds of animals and birds fill the forest atmosphere.
Music plays softly as two people walk on a forest path.
Music plays softly as two people walk through the forest.
Music plays softly in the background as he speaks.
Music plays softly in the background as four people stand in a field.
Music plays softly in the background.
Soft music plays as a person walks through tall grass.
Music plays softly in the background as they converse in the field.
Soft music plays as three women stand in a serene field.
Soft music plays in the background as three women stand in a field.
Birds chirp in the background as two men stand on the shore.
Birds chirp in the background as two women stand by water.
Wild animals and birds are heard near the water.
A woman in a white saree stands distressed by the water.
Birds and a duck squawk near the distressed woman by water.
A frog croaks in the background.
Birds chirp in the background as three people sit on the ground.
Music plays softly in the background.
Music plays softly in the background as four people sit together.
Music plays softly in the background as people gather in the woods.
Music plays softly in the background of the rural scene.
Music plays softly in the background.
Romantic music plays as the couple smiles in their embrace.
Soft music plays in the background as they embrace and smile.
Birds chirp softly in the background.
Birds sing and insects buzz as the couple embraces.
Soft music plays as the sun sets over palm trees.
Soft music plays as the sunset paints the sky pink and orange.
Music plays softly as people walk through the field.
Music plays softly as people walk through tall grass.
Music plays softly as people walk through the tall grass.
Music plays softly in the background.
Background music plays softly.
Insects buzz nearby as the man and woman look concerned.
Men stand in a field, chopping wood while wild animals sound nearby.
Sounds of animals and water fill the background.
Farm animals and livestock make ambient sounds in the background.
Animals scratch in the forest as people sit nearby.
Animal sounds echo in the forest where people sit together.
Animals are heard in the forest where people sit together.
Sounds of animals and insects fill the forested area.
Birds sing and environmental sounds fill the forested area.
Sounds of animals and birds fill the forested area.
Insects buzz softly as people sit under the wooden structure.
Birds are chirping in the background as people sit nearby.
Birds chirp softly as two concerned women stand by a tree.
Two concerned women stand by a tree, one in a white headscarf.
Music plays softly in the background.
Music plays softly in the background as she stands by a cow.
Music plays softly as four women sit on the ground.
Soft music plays in the background with wind instruments.
Music plays softly in the background.
Theremin music plays softly in the background.
Cattle moo nearby as a small hut stands by the path.
Pattering sounds of rodents, including rats and mice, are heard.
Sitar music plays softly in the background.