Ambient noise fills the background during Episode 16's introduction.
Birds chirp in the background amidst the lush greenery.
Birds chirp in a lush, green environment with thick trees.
Birds chirp softly in the background of the forest.
Birds sing as a person walks through the forest.
Two women stand in a field, looking at each other.
Birds chirp in the background as two men stand together.
A crow caws in the distance.
Ambient animal sounds fill the scene.
A young boy peeks out from behind a tree in the woods.
Music plays softly as the person walks through the tall grass.
Music plays softly as a person walks through tall grass.
Tabla music plays softly in the background.
Music plays softly in the background.
The tabla plays softly in the background.
Music and tabla play softly in the background.
A crow caws in the distance as the man walks.
Laughter echoes in the background.
Animal sounds are heard in the background.
Wild animals and birds make ambient sounds in the background.
An owl hoots and other animals make sounds.
Crows caw and birds chirp as they smile together.
Music plays softly in the background as they converse.
Wind blows gently through the trees in the forest.
Music plays softly in the background as they sit on the mat.
Music plays softly in the background as they sit under the tree.
Birds chirp as three people sit on a bamboo mat.
Music plays softly in the background as three people sit together.
Music plays softly as a person walks on a dirt path.
Music plays softly as people walk along a forest path.
Music plays softly as three people walk through a grassy field.
Music plays softly in the background as four people stand in a field.
Music plays softly in the background as two men sit facing each other.
Soft music plays as a person walks through tall grass.
Music plays as a person walks through tall grass.
Soft music plays as a woman walks through tall grass.
Music plays softly as two women stand in a grassy field.
Music plays softly as two women stand in a tall grass field.
Birds sing while a man and woman kneel in the field.
Birds chirp softly in the background near the water.
A woman stands by the water, listening to birds and animals.
A woman in a white saree stands distressed by the water.
Birds chirp in the background as the woman stands by the water.
Frogs croak and birds chirp in the wooded area.
Birds chirp in the background as three people sit in the woods.
Music plays softly in the background as three people sit.
Music plays softly in the background as three people sit under a tree.
Music plays softly in the background.
Music plays softly in the background as four people sit together.
Music plays as a group dances in the forest.
Music plays softly in the background.
Music plays softly in the background of the wooded scene.
Romantic music plays softly in the background.
Romantic music plays softly in the background as they embrace.
Animal sounds are heard in the background.
Ambient sounds of rodents and insects fill the air.
Soft music plays as the sun sets in a pink-orange sky.
Music plays softly as people walk through the field.
Music plays softly as people walk through the tall grass.
Music plays softly as people walk through golden brown grass.
Music plays softly in the background of the golden field.
Music plays softly as people walk through the dry grass field.
Music plays softly as people walk through tall, dry grass.
Music plays softly as a group walks through tall grass.
Music plays softly as six people walk through tall grass.
Music plays softly in the background.
Insects buzz nearby as two men stand seriously in the field.
Men stand in a field as birds sing nearby.
Sounds of livestock and farm animals fill the rural atmosphere.
People sit in the forest, engaged in conversation and scratching.
People converse in a forest while animals and vehicles are nearby.
Sounds of animals echo in the forest around the group.
People converse in a forest while animals scurry nearby.
Birds sing and environmental sounds fill the forested area.
Whistling sounds accompany a group engaged in conversation on the ground.
Birds chirp while the wind rustles through the trees.
Insects buzz as people sit under a wooden structure in the forest.
Insects buzz nearby as people sit under a wooden structure.
A frog croaks as she stands deep in thought by the tree.
Frogs croak and birds chirp as she stands deep in thought.
She stands by a tree trunk, lost in thought.
Music plays softly in the background.
Soft music plays in the background as a young woman stands.
Music plays softly in the background as two women sit outside.
Soft music plays in the background as two women sit together.
Music plays softly in the background.
Music plays softly in the background of the tropical garden.
Cattle moo softly near a winding dirt path in the garden.
Pattering sounds of rodents are heard in the background.
Music plays softly in the background.